<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DeadCode Manifesto on</title><link>https://dambasement.net/</link><description>Recent content in DeadCode Manifesto on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dambasement.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Certified Red Team Operator</title><link>https://dambasement.net/posts/08-01-2023-crto/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dambasement.net/posts/08-01-2023-crto/</guid><description>Welcome back! Today I want to talk about CRTO certification I recently achieved.
Googling for CRTO (Certified Red Team Operator), there are dozens of reviews explaining the exam, the lab and the course offered by ZeroPoint Security and RastaMouse. I really do not want to reinvent the wheel for the umpteenth time but instead, to propose an approach that I have hardly found out there and which is working in my case, hoping this can be useful or encouraging for you too!</description></item><item><title>Vintage TV</title><link>https://dambasement.net/posts/26-12-2022-television/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dambasement.net/posts/26-12-2022-television/</guid><description>Welcome back! Hi there, and Merry XMas!
When I decided to create a site to introduce myself I had a small personal challenge into my mind: to be able to create something attractive with as few lines of code as possible LOL. The result can be seen on my github page and on my Behance page.
It&amp;rsquo;s nothing more than a nice and unpretentious showcase that wants to present the people who use it in a captivating and exciting way, especially for nostalgics like me who grew up between the 80&amp;rsquo;s and 90&amp;rsquo;s.</description></item><item><title>Greetings</title><link>https://dambasement.net/posts/11-12-2022-greetings/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dambasement.net/posts/11-12-2022-greetings/</guid><description>and there it is&amp;hellip; Hi there! I got it! Finally.
This is my first post, just an introduction and a chance to say hello!
I will try to share fun and useful news, topics and themes here. Even though I&amp;rsquo;m quite new to blogging, I&amp;rsquo;ll do my best to create something nice.
Thanks to everyone will take some time to check it and give it a read.
I will update my twitter account every time a new post will be released so, don&amp;rsquo;t forget to follow me at</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://dambasement.net/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dambasement.net/about/</guid><description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m DeadCode.
Infosec dude, based in Rome, working in cybersec since 2015. I am involved in penetration testing, ethical hacking and red teaming tasks on a daily basis. Cybersec Hackaton lover. CTF player. 🥸
Check my blog for my last updates about my works, my life, things I like and activities I enjoy. My git repo links are somewhere in this site, you can check there about my projects. I will also post stuff in the blog section, trying to be as much regular as possible in terms of updates and news.</description></item></channel></rss>